Ali Jahankah

Full-Stack Web Dev

PROFILE

I am a problem solving, teamworkoriented and Creative bilingual FullStack Web Developer with 2 years of
experience. Very keen to build a career
and gain further experience of; taking a lead role in maintaining and
developing a site. Running online
sessions for other students to teach
them and transfer my knowledge to
them. Carrying out quality assurance
checks on content. Available with a
one-week notice period

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript / ES6, jQuery,
React.js, Bootstrap, MongoDB Compass,
Redux/Redux-Thunk, Axios, Node.js,
Express.js, PostgreSQL,

React Router, Form Validation, API's and REST API's.

CONTACT

Mitcham London | CR4 07576790138 alijahankhah8@gmail.com

Social (clickable)

GitHub LinkedIn

Interest | Hobbies

I am interested in coding tricks and playing guitar. I spend part of my time on learning and coding every day as I am determined to build a career in this industry

Excellent References are available on request

WORK EXPERIENCE

Barista Notes Coffee | London Dec 2021 - to present
Working in busy popular local coffee shop. Each day greeting customers
and making them feel welcome. Delivering high-quality customer
service at lightning speed with visually appealing presentation including
latte art.

Waiter Abshar Restaurant, London Nov 2019 – March 2020 working efficiently with team members to ensure all tables received excellent service, providing assistance to colleagues when required. Always aware of guest satisfaction to deliver the perfect service experience.

Volunteer West Croydon Baptist Church 2018 - to present
Explaining tasks to the new Volunteers. Working together in a team to help
Refugees with food, clothes and so on.

Owner Uaral Internet Café / Iran Feb 2017-Nov 2017
helping customers with various queries regarding email account and other
online queries like restoring files, registrations. I improved my resilience, selfconfident, time management and communication there as I was working hard
and I was the owner.

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Developer Cou	rse Code Your Future	Sep 2021
Full-Stack Developer	self-taught learner	May 2020 to present
English Functional	South Thames College	2020
GCSE in Math	South Thames College	2019
Agriculture	Shiraz University/Iran	2015-2017
	Projects (clickable)	

CYF-Hotel React- responsive

<u>CYF-Full-Stack</u> React, Context, Node, Express, PostgreSQL, responsive

<u>Chat-Server</u> React, Context, Node, Express, PostgreSQL

Birthday HTML, CSS, JS, responsive

Currently working on a Full-Stack project for a charity. Click here please

Thank you!